Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
Despair and Hope
Episode 46
How did you manage to return unscathed after falling into the Bottomless Abyss?
What?
You’ve grown stronger.
What exactly did you go through in the Bottomless Abyss?
Then I’ll tell you exactly what I went through.
Someone else has fallen down here.
He’s waking up.
Hello there.
W-what is this thing?
My hands…my body…
What’s going on?
Calm down first.
Now, let’s invite Brother Dahuang to answer your questions and clear up your confusion.
Brother Dahuang?
Hello there. I’m Brother Dahuang.
I’m the wisest one around here.
Whatever questions you have, I can answer them.
A cockroach that can talk? Stay away from me!
Who are you calling a cockroach? Honestly…
I’m a resident of this world.
Sorry, sorry.
You said you’re a resident…But why do you look like this?
And besides…
Why live in a place like this?
I forgot! I only remember falling and ending up here.
You see, anyone who falls from above into the abyss…
gradually loses their physical features as they fall.
Before falling into this Bottomless Abyss,
we had whole bodies, too.
But as time went by,
our bodies slowly faded away
until we became like this.
Don’t cry…please don’t cry.
My head is in such a mess.
How…how exactly did I fall in here?
Why can’t I remember anything?
Will I end up looking like you guys too?
You’re actually quite lucky.
Usually, anyone who falls into the abyss gets sucked straight into the black hole.
A black hole?
Over here—over here, over here, over here.
This black hole looks pretty quiet.
It looks quiet right now,
but it erupts periodically.
When it erupts, it sucks up everything in the vicinity.
So, that’s the black hole that sucked me in.
By the way, is it safe for you guys to stay here?
It’s actually not safe.
The day before yesterday, the black hole erupted.
Xiao Zhu and his safe house were sucked away.
A few days before that, it was Auntie Green.
And then…
So what are we waiting for?
Let’s get out of this…what was it called? The Heartless…
It’s the Bottomless Abyss.
Right, let’s escape this Bottomless Abyss.
Escape?
Those who once shared your idea…
now have nothing left here but their names.
Their bodies were all sucked into the black hole.
You’d better stop messing around.
We need to reinforce the safe house before the next black hole eruption.
Come and help out.
That’s how you survive in the Bottomless Abyss.
Sparky…
I can’t stay here.
My friends are waiting for me…I still have to…
What was it I had to do?
Why can’t I remember?
This place slowly eats away at our memories.
For those of us who’ve stayed too long,
we end up forgetting everything.
I…I can’t forget my friend. I have to leave this place.
I have to get out of here—and fast.
That was just a trial run; now it’s for real.
He fell down again.
What’s there to watch?
He’ll probably give up soon.
Are you going to keep going?
Of course.
You remind me of someone.
Back then, he was just as determined to climb up as you are.
Did he succeed?
He…
I don’t remember.
Regardless of whether that person made it up,
I am definitely going to climb up there.
Climbing so high…
There’s no way he’ll make it up.
He fell back down.
See? Just look.
You should just give up; the gaps in your body are getting bigger.
If you keep struggling like this, you’ll soon turn into mere lines.
You’d be better off saving your energy
to survive the next black hole eruption.
That’s more like it.
Gather some materials and help us build a safe house.
I refuse to believe I can’t climb it with this thing.
You still haven’t given up?
You’ve failed so many times already.
Why won’t you just give up?
My friends need me, so…
I absolutely cannot give up.
“Friends”?
Is that something tasty?
How long do you think it’ll take for him to fall?
Definitely no more than ten seconds.
He’s held on for so long this time.
I actually think he might make it to the top this time.
He’s almost there.
Let me see.
I want to see too.
Go, Sparky!
Go!
Go, go!
He’s so close.
He fell.
Look, everyone!
Sparky is still up there.
Go, go!
He did it!
He actually made it.
I told you he’d climb up there.
You never said that.
I said it in my head.
What is he doing coming down? He’s coming down.
What’s wrong with him?
He’s giving up, obviously.
I knew he’d do this.
But he was so determined just a moment ago.
It’s so disappointing.
You finally made it up there—why are you coming back?
I came back to take you all out of here.
But we’ve only just met.
You don’t need to turn back for us.
Staying here means getting swallowed by the black hole sooner or later.
That’s why I want to take everyone up with me.
Thanks for the kind offer.
But we’ll just stay here.
We used to dream of hope, too.
But every time, we were met only with despair.
We’ve become like this now.
We no longer dare to hope.
To give up hope so easily,
what about the family and friends waiting for you outside?
Their worry, their hope, their anticipation—
aren’t those the very forces driving us to climb higher?
Don’t you want to see them again?
But we’ve all lost our memories.
Then let’s get those memories back together.
Every memory of our friends and family
and all our own memories, too.
Alert! Alert! The black hole is erupting!
Everyone, hurry to the safe house!
It’s erupting earlier than last time.
Let go of me. You might actually survive if you’re on your own.
I can’t do that.
I would never abandon my companions.
Don’t let go.
This…
Sparky, forget about us.
No.
You’d have a fighting chance if you escaped on your own.
I said I’d get you all out of here.
Sparky, your body…
Don’t worry, I can hold on.
I was
going to take everyone
take everyone
to…
…take them where?
Why can’t I remember?
What…what am I holding on for?
Sparky…
Sparky…Sparky
Sparky, over here.
Sparky, just give up.
You can’t catch up on the score with the time left.
You never know who’ll win until the very last moment.
Go, Daddy!
The hoop here…
has disappeared.
Where did everyone go?
How did they all vanish?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5…
Great, everyone’s okay.
Wait, I remember I had…
You’re awake.
That’s great.
Sparky.
We were so worried about you.
It was really dangerous back there.
No wonder I’m still here.
Thanks for saving me.
No, we should be thanking you for saving us.
It’s just that the safe house is completely destroyed.
Since there’s no way back, why not come up with me?
Sparky can get us safely through the black hole eruption.
So maybe he really can take us up there.
Rest assured, I will definitely get us up there.
For the sake of the family and friends who are waiting for us.
To be continued